<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-25T01:20:52.442Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2023-04-25T01:20:52.442Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use ChatGPT – Prompts for Data Scientists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-for-data-scientists/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-for-data-scientists/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T23:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, many people are concerned with the way AI is evolving. They see it effortlessly solving problems, performing tasks quickly and accurately, and doing jobs easily and efficiently.  And while some people are scared, others are actually embracing it. I'm one of those people who are embracing it,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shittu Olumide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Server Side Rendering in JavaScript – SSR vs CSR Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-side-rendering-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-side-rendering-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T22:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of Server Side Rendering (SSR) is often misunderstood. So my aim in this article is to bring clarity to this process and how it works.  Here's what we'll cover in this guide:  1. What is server side rendering? What are its pros and cons when compared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Pointers in Go? A Guide for JavaScript Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-pointers-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-pointers-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T22:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming from a language like JavaScript, pointers can be kind of confusing at first. Here I will break it down so that they are easier to understand. What Are Pointers in Go? Just like in JavaScript, Go has variables which are locations in memory that store a value.  In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Barrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Your Code Like a Competitive Programmer –Automate and Save Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debugging-like-competitive-programmers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/debugging-like-competitive-programmers/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T22:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been a competitive programmer for many years. And during that time, I have faced the process of debugging on numerous occasions.  In this article, I will try to describe how debugging works in such environments, instead of depicting it in the regular software development activities we do every]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Gonzalez Rosales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Redux Toolkit to Manage State in Your React Application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-redux-toolkit-to-manage-state-in-react-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-redux-toolkit-to-manage-state-in-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T21:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State management is one of the most important things you'll deal with in front end development.  You can manage state in React in various ways. Some examples include using state in class components, using React hooks such as useState and useEffect hook, using the Context API, or using Redux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Oghenetejiri Ukumakube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Google Apps Script – Build a Paint By Numbers Spreadsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-google-apps-script-build-a-paint-by-numbers-spreadsheet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-google-apps-script-build-a-paint-by-numbers-spreadsheet/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T21:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spreadsheets are great for financial modeling, but they're also capable of displaying pixel art.  In this Apps Script tutorial, we'll build a paint by numbers spreadsheet using conditional formatting and a script that "paints" a blank spreadsheet. You'll learn how to:  1. Import data  2. Apply proper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React Router 6 in Ten Hours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-router-6-3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-router-6-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T20:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React Router is a powerful library that helps you build single-page applications with ease. It allows you to create multiple routes, nested routes, and handle transitions between them, all while maintaining a clean and organized codebase. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Boost Your Creativity – Strategies for Generating Ideas and Overcoming Writer's Block]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-overcome-writers-block-and-boost-creativity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-overcome-writers-block-and-boost-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T19:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you ever find yourself stuck when it comes to writing or unable to come up with creative solutions to a problem? Don’t worry—you are not alone. Everyone experiences writer's block or a lack of creativity at some point. At times, as writers, we may be really eager to write]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is RAM? How to Access Your Computer's RAM and Read the Contents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-and-read-ram-contents/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-access-and-read-ram-contents/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T19:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a comprehensive guide on how to read the contents of your computer's RAM.  Random Access Memory (RAM) is a crucial component of any computer system, and it is responsible for temporarily storing data that is required by the system to carry out its functions. But the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Visualization with Matplotlib – a Step by Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-data-vizualization-using-matplotlib/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introduction-to-data-vizualization-using-matplotlib/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T18:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEE [https://tv.apple.com/us/show/see/umc.cmc.3s4mgg2y7h95fks9gnc4pw13m] is a beautiful Apple TV series that depicts a dystopia where humans have lost their sight. Hundreds of years later, it was considered a myth that people could ever see.  Jason Momoa is one of the leads and plays Baba Voss, an elite warrior. Jason's wife gives]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MENE-EJEGI OGBEMI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potentially Dangerous Non-Accessibility Of Cookie Notices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potentially-dangerous-non-accessibility-cookie-notices/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this piece, a Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) auditor shares some cookie banner error patterns that can massively hurt a page’s overall conformance. Let’s explore what to look out for with this omnipresent piece of the web interface.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcus Herrmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring The Potential Of Web Workers For Multithreading On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/potential-web-workers-multithreading-web/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Sarah Oke Okolo explores the importance of Web Workers for multithreading on the web, including the limitations and considerations of using them and the strategies for mitigating potential issues associated with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sarah Oke Okolo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building And Dockerizing A Node.js App With Stateless Architecture With Help From Kinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/building-dockerizing-nodejs-app-stateless-architecture-kinsta/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing your Node.js apps can lead to smashing success—offering consistency, easy debugging, and hassle-free dependency management. When you host this container on Kinsta, you also benefit from high-speed performance, robust security, and top-notch scalability. By combining these two, you'll surely have a whale of a time as you sail smoothly through the development seas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tejas Kumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Mechanics In UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/color-mechanics-ui-kits/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adel Khamatov shares a model of color mechanics that he came up with during research on developing UI kits and illustrates an approach to solving related problems with best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adel Khamatov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 59 With Chiara Aliotta: What Is Design Storytelling?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/smashing-podcast-episode-59/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Smashing Podcast, we take a look at design storytelling. What is it, and how can it help us shape digital experiences? Vitaly talks to Chiara Aliotta to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Design Thinking?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/what-is-design-thinking/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if things could have been done differently? But not sure how? Well, then, do not fall in love with the solution, but fall in love with the problem! Here’s an article to dive deep into how design thinking could do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Krithika Subramanian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passkeys: What the Heck and Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=377305</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/passkeys-what-the-heck-and-why/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-12T17:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These things called passkeys sure are making the rounds these days. They were a main attraction at W3C TPAC 2022, gained support in Safari 16, are finding their way into macOS and iOS, and are slated to …
Passkeys: What the Heck and Why? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal Fennimore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design An Effective User Onboarding Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/design-effective-user-onboarding-flow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to maximize conversions or collect necessary user information for other purposes, a user onboarding flow is necessary. In this article, you will learn how, with the help of Feathery, to design an effective user onboarding flow for your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Suzanne Scacca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Your App With A Threat Model Based On JSONDiff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/protect-app-threat-model-jsondiff/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a developer who wants to concentrate on delivering a killer application rather than worrying about countless security issues, threat model documents can help you do that. With small architectural changes, we can make these threats manageable and prevent them in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zack Grossbart &amp; Terry Yao)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Algorithms: Skills Of Designers That AI Can’t Replicate]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/04/skills-designers-ai-cant-replicate/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights non-technical skills like curiosity, observation, empathy, advocacy, visual communication, and collaboration that designers routinely use in their process to make a difference through design. AI can be used to augment designers’ workflow instead of replacing people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing Into April (2023 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With April just around the corner, we have a new collection of desktop and mobile wallpapers waiting for you to celebrate the beginning of the new month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, the wallpapers come in versions with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Checklist For Running Design Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/organizing-design-workshops-checklist/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workshops are all about people: they involve people, are conducted by people, and aim to close the gaps in people’s communication. Slava Shestopalov shares a checklist with everything you need to keep in mind when running a workshop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Slava Shestopalov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-Grained Access Handling And Data Management With Row-Level Security]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/access-handling-data-management-row-level-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-29T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with sensitive data is an important topic for any app. In this article, you will find out how to handle sensitive or confidential information in your apps and what Row-Level Security means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Handoff Is No Handoff]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2023/03/best-handoff-is-no-handoff/"/>
        <updated>2023-03-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design handoffs are inefficient and painful. They cause frustration, friction and a lot of back and forth. Can we avoid them altogether? Of course we can! Let’s see how to do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>